seopartner.com 2016-12-03

# SEOPartner Privacy Notice — SEOPartner

[last updated May 2016]

This Privacy Notice should be read in conjunction with our [terms and conditions](http://seopartner.com/terms/).

**Our privacy commitment**  
If you are visiting this page you may have been directed from one of Our Websites . We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm and continuing commitment to the privacy of personal information provided by those visiting and interacting with any website controlled by SEOPartner. We hold the privacy of your personal information in the highest regard. This notice sets out how we collect, use and safeguard your personal information to assist you in making informed decisions when using oursites. This policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers’ needs.  
SEOPartner complies with Australian privacy law.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice**  
We may change this Privacy Notice from time to time. If/when changes are made, we will email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. Please be assured that if the terms of our Privacy Notice change in the future, we will not use your personal information in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Notice without your prior consent.

**Your Consent**  
By using Our Website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Notice. The Privacy Notice that applies to you is that notice that is current when you provide information to us or we collect personal information.

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
When you visit these websites you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Our Website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse Our Website.

## 1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

**Registration Information**  
When you register for any of our products, services or newsletters you will provide us information about yourself.

**Credit Card Information**  
If you choose to use our Services, you may need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following information:  
-Name  
-Mailing address  
-Email address  
-Credit card number  
-Name on credit card  
-Credit card billing address  
-Business and home phone number

**Storage of Credit Card Information**  
Credit cards are processed via either Paypal or a Bank merchant facility and stored in a SSL secure environment with [Nanacast](http://nanacast.com/index.php?&req=doc&id=10001).

**Email Information**  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

**Testimonials**  
If you provide us with a testimonial, you give us your consent for the use of your name and the Service to be displayed on Our Website or in our other marketing material, together with the content of the testimonial that you provide.

**Collecting sensitive information**  
We do not actively collect sensitive information about you, including information about your health, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, sexual orientation or criminal history. We will take steps to appropriately protect any sensitive information we do receive.

## 2\. Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial websites, Our Website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and tracking “pixels” (see explanation below, “What Are Cookies/Pixels?”) and web server log files to collect information about how Our Website is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at Our Website, and the websites visited just before and just after Our Website.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**  
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing the products and services you requested, to process your payment, to monitor the use of the service, our marketing and promotional efforts and improve our content and service offerings, and customize Our Website’s content, layout, services and for other lawful purposes. These uses improve our site and better tailor it to meet your needs.  
Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.  
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Website, new Services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by updating your subscription settings or issuing a ticket at [www.SuperFastHelp.com ](http://www.superfasthelp.com/)

**What Are Cookies/Pixels?**  
A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that site’s computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you may alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of Our Website will not function as effectively. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive or pass on computer viruses.  
A tracking pixel communicates with a cookie to collect or deliver information. It does not identify you personally, but may result in you receiving re-targeted advertising from websites you have already visited. To find out how to opt out of tailored advertising please check the options available here – <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>

**How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?**  
As you visit and browse Our Website, the Our Website uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server log files or pixels, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting Our Website and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve Our Website and better serve our clients. Cookies and pixels do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.

**IP Addresses**  
IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**Sharing and Selling Information**  
We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide Services that you have requested.

**Cookie Based Marketing**  
Some of our advertising campaigns may track users across different websites for the purpose of displaying advertising. We do not know which specific website are used in these campaigns, but you should assume tracking occurs, and if this is an issue you should turn-off third party cookies in your web browser. To find out how to opt out of tailored advertising please check the options available here – <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>

**What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?**  
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our terms and conditions or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.

**What About Other Websites Linked to Our Website?**  
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from Our Website. Please remember that when you use a link to go from Our Website to another web site, our Privacy Notice is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites, which have a link on Our Website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Social Networking Services and links to other websites**  
We may provide links to other websites or use social networking services such as Twitter and Facebook to communicate with the public about our work. These sites have their own privacy policies. When you communicate with us using these services we may collect your personal information. We will only use it to help us to communicate with you and the public. The social networking service will also handle your personal information for its own purposes.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in Australia and the United States. The laws on holding personal data in Australia and the United States may be less stringent than the laws of your Country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
If we work with contractors outside Australia to assist us in delivering Services to you, we require those contractors to adhere to our requirements and obligations around the security of your personal information.

**Choice/Opt-In/Opt-Out**  
This site allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**A Special Note About Children**  
Children are not eligible to use our services unsupervised and we ask that children (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor, you can use this service only in conjunction with permission and guidance from your parents or guardians.

**Acquisition or Changes in Ownership**  
In the event that the web site (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**  
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by issuing a ticket at [www.SuperFastHelp.com](http://www.superfasthelp.com/)

**Problems?**  
If you have any concerns about our use of your personal information, please contact us and let us know what the problem is. We will respond to your concerns as soon as we can.

If you are not happy with how we manage your concerns, you can contact the Australian Privacy Commission, available at [http://www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/).
